<resources>
    <string name="app_name">David AI</string>

    <!-- Model display names shown to users -->
    <string name="model_lite">David AI Lite</string>
    <string name="model_1b">David AI 1B</string>
    <string name="model_2b">David AI 2B</string>
    <string name="model_unknown">David AI</string>

    <string name="privacy_policy_text">DAVID AI — PRIVACY POLICY
Last updated: March 2026

1. NO DATA COLLECTION
David AI does not collect, store, transmit, or share any personal data. This includes but is not limited to: conversation history, voice recordings, location data, device identifiers, usage statistics, or any other personal information.

2. ON-DEVICE PROCESSING
All AI inference runs entirely on your device using on-device language models via MLC-LLM. Your conversations never leave your phone. No server receives your messages.

3. LOCATION
Location access (GPS) is used only to provide contextual answers (e.g. local weather). Location data is processed locally and is never transmitted to any server.

4. MICROPHONE
Microphone access is used only for voice input via Android SpeechRecognizer. We do not record, store, or transmit audio.

5. INTERNET ACCESS
The app uses internet access only for:
   \u2022 Fetching weather data from Open-Meteo (anonymous)
   \u2022 Fetching news headlines from Google News RSS (anonymous)
   \u2022 Displaying Google AdMob ads (governed by Google\u2019s privacy policy)
   \u2022 Optional: downloading model weights on first launch

6. ADVERTISING
David AI uses Google AdMob for advertising. You can opt out via Android Settings \u2192 Google \u2192 Ads.

7. OPEN SOURCE
David AI is fully open source:
https://github.com/david0154/NexuzyAI-Android

8. CHILDREN\u2019S PRIVACY
Since we collect no data at all, this app is safe for all ages.

9. CONTACT
For any privacy concerns:
\u2022 nexuzylab@gmail.com
\u2022 davidk76011@gmail.com

Developed by David \u2022 Managed by Nexuzy Lab
MIT License \u00a9 2025\u20132026</string>

</resources>
